Guide to the Anspach Travel Bureau Collection of Tourism Literature, 1936-2014 and undated RL.00045
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- United States, 1936-2014 and undated; 11; 52 boxes
  - Arkansas, 182
    - General, 1963-1996 and undated (Box USA7)
  - California, 183
    - General, 1987-1990 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Big Sur, 1995-2001 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Buena Park (including Knott's Berry Farm), 1977-1990 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Carlsbad, 1988-2005 (Box USA7)
    - Carmel, 1990-2014 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Catalina, 1984-1992 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Central coast, undated (Box USA8)
    - Coronado, undated (Box USA8)
    - Dana Point/Monarch Beach, 1992-2003 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Death Valley/Furnace Creek, 1986 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Disneyland, 1960s-2002 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Hermosa/Half Moon Bay, 2000 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Indian Wells, 1998-2002 and undated (Box USA8)
    - La Jolla/Torrey Pines, 1989-2003 and undated (Box USA8)
    - La Quinta, 1993-2004 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Laguna Beach, 1991-2005 and undated (Box USA8)
    - Laguna Beach, 1991-2005 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Lake Tahoe (includes some Nevada sites), 1981-2000 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Los Angeles--General, 1963-2003 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Los Angeles--Airport, 1970s-1985 (Box USA9)
    - Los Angeles--Beverly Hills, 1996-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA9)
    - Los Angeles--Getty Center, 1981-2001 (Box USA9)
    - Los Angeles--Hollywood, 1980-1996 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Los Angeles--Hotels, 1978-2000 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Marina Del Rey, 1980 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Marineland, 1984-1986 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Mendocino area, 2000 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Monterey, 1986-1998 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Moss Beach/Seal Cove Inn, 1992 and undated (Box USA9)
    - Napa Valley, 1988-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA10)
    - Newport Beach, 1986-1991 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Northern California area, 1990-1996 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Oakland, 1976-1984 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Ojai, 1988-2001 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Palm Springs, 1986-1996 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Parks and forests, 1949-1992 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Pasadena, 2003 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Pebble Beach, 1976-1998 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Rancho La Costa, 1990 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Rancho Valencia, 1995-2000 and undated (Box USA10)
    - Sacramento, 1980-1984 and undated (Box USA10)
    - San Diego, 1975-2001 and undated (Box USA10)
    - San Francisco, 1987-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA11)
    - San Jose, 1978-1990 and undated (Box USA11)
    - San Simeon, 1989 and undated (Box USA11)
    - Santa Barbara, 1978-2005 and undated (Box USA11)
    - Santa Monica, 1990-2004 and undated (Box USA11)
    - Solvang, 1985-1990 and undated (Box USA11)
    - Sonoma, 1983-2005 and undated (Box USA11)
    - Southern California, 1970s-2005 and undated (Box USA11)
    - Wine country, 1983-2001 and undated (Box USA12)
    - Yosemite, 1976-1997 and undated (Box USA12)
  - Colorado, 184
    - General, 1966-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box USA12)
    - Aspen--General, 1986-2005 and undated (Box USA12)
    - Aspen--Condominiums, 1989-2001 (Box USA12)
    - Aspen--Hotels, 1983-2000 and undated (Box USA12)
    - Aspen--Snowmass, 2000-2002 and undated (Box USA12)
    - Beaver Creek, 1983-2004 and undated (Box USA12)
    - Beaver Creek, 1983-2004 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Boulder, 1983-2005 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Breckenridge, 1985-2000 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Colorado Springs--General, 1986-2000 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Colorado Springs--Broadmoor, 1992-2005 (Box USA13)
    - Copper Mountain/Crested Butte, 1987-1999 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Denver, 1990-2000 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Durango, 1987-1995 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Estes Park, 1985-1995 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Fort Collins, 1995 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Keystone, 1993-2002 and undated (Box USA13)
    - Manitou Springs, undated (Box USA13)
    - Pagosa Springs, undated (Box USA13)
    - Parks, 1957-1992 and undated (Box USA14)
    - Steamboat Springs, 1978-2002 and undated (Box USA14)
    - Telluride, 1988-2003 and undated (Box USA14)
    - Vail--General, 1989-2004 and undated (Box USA14)
    - Vail--Hotels, 1986-2000 and undated (Box USA14)
    - Winter Park, 1977-2001 and undated (Box USA14)
  - Connecticut, 185
    - General, 1967-1996 and undated (Box USA14)
  - District of Columbia, 186
    - General, 1973-2002 and undated (Box USA14)
    - Hotels, 1977-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA15)
    - Maps, 1956-2000 (Box USA15)
  - Florida, 187
    - General, 1970-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA15)
    - General--Travel planning, 1996-2006 (Box USA15)
    - Amelia Island, 1987-2003 and undated (Box USA15)
    - Aventura/Turnberry, 1994-2004 and undated (Box USA15)
    - Bal Harbor, 1997 (Box USA16)
    - Boca Raton, 1980-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA16)
    - Cape Haze, 1991 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Captiva Island, 1998-2001 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Clearwater/Belleview, 1982-2001 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Cypress Gardens, 1989-1994 (Box USA16)
    - Daytona Beach, 1985-2000 (Box USA16)
    - Delray/Deerfield/Destin, 1970s-2005 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Disney World--Activities and general, 1992-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA16)
    - Disney World--Disney Cruise Line, 2005 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Disney World--Disney Travel Company, 2002-2006 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Disney World--Lodging--Disney Resorts and Hotels, 1988-2000 and undated (Box USA16)
    - Disney World--Lodging--Kissimmee, 1986-1996 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Disney World--Lodging--Lake Buena Vista, 1986-1993 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Disney World--Lodging--Wedding planning, 1995-2004 (Box USA17)
    - Everglades, 1974-1996 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Fisher Island, undated (Box USA17)
    - Florida Keys, 1969-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA17)
    - Fort Lauderdale, 1972-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA17)
    - Fort Myers, 1985-2001 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Grenelefe, 1980-1987 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Hawk's Cay, 1992-2001 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Indian River Plantation, undated (Box USA17)
    - Islamadora--General, 1990-1994 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Islamadora--Cheeca Lodge, 1991-2000 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Jupiter, 1977-1985 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Key Biscayne, 1988 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Key Largo, 1994-2003 and undated (Box USA17)
    - Key West, 1990-2004 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Lee Island Coast, 1995-2003 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Little Palm Island, 1999-2003 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Longboat Key, 1996-2005 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Marco Island, 1990-1996 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Miami--General, 1964-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA18)
    - Miami--Coconut Grove, 1991-2001 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Miami--Miami Beach, 1988-1998 and undated (Box USA18)
    - Miami--South Beach, 2001-2006 and undated (Box USA19)
    - Naples--General, 1994-2003 and undated (Box USA19)
    - Naples--Ritz-Carlton, 1997-2004 and undated (Box USA19)
    - Orlando--General, 1978-2003 and undated (Box USA19)
    - Orlando--Hotels, 1985-2001 and undated (Box USA19)
    - Orlando--Universal Studios, 1999-2006 (Box USA19)
    - Orlando--Universal Studios--Portofino Bay, 1999-2005 (Box USA19)
    - Palm Beach--General, 1958-2004; 3 folders (Box USA20)
    - Palm Beach--Hotels, 1994-2004 and undated (Box USA20)
    - Parks, 1972-1993 (Box USA20)
    - Pompano Beach, 1972-1983 and undated (Box USA20)
    - Ponte Vedra, 1989-2003 and undated (Box USA20)
    - Port St. Lucie, 1965-1971 (Box USA20)
    - St. Petersburg, 1972-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA20)
    - Sanibel Island/Sanibel Beach, 1974-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA20)
    - Sarasota, 1965-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA20)
    - Silver Springs, 1977-1982 (Box USA20)
    - Tampa, 1970s-2001 (Box USA20)
    - Vistana, 1991 and undated (Box USA20)
  - Georgia, 188
    - Atlanta, 1991-1994 and undated (Box USA21)
    - Calloway Gardens, 1984-2003 and undated (Box USA21)
    - Destinations, 1975-2001 and undated (Box USA21)
    - Jekyll Island, 2005 and undated (Box USA21)
    - St. Simons Island, undated (Box USA21)
    - Savannah, 1988-2004 and undated (Box USA21)
    - Sea Island, 1993-2006 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA21)
  - Hawaii, 189
    - General, 1950s-1975 (Box USA21)
    - General--Activities, 1981-1997 and undated (Box USA21)
    - General--Hotels, 1984-2005 and undated (Box USA21)
    - General--Maps, 1981-1983 and undated (Box USA21)
    - General--Travel planning, 2001-2004 and undated (Box USA22)
    - General--Visitors Bureau publications, 1984-2005; 3 folders (Box USA22)
    - General--Volcano parks, 2002 (Box USA22)
    - Big Island (Hawaii)--General, 1967-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA22)
    - Big Island (Hawaii)--Hilo, 1973-1979 and undated (Box USA22)
    - Big Island (Hawaii)--Kona, 1970-2004 (Box USA23)
    - Big Island (Hawaii)--Mauna Kea, 1984-2003 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Big Island (Hawaii)--Mauna Lani, 1984-1999 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Big Island (Hawaii)--Waikoloa, 1987-2001 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Kauai--General, 1962-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA23)
    - Kauai--General--Hotels, 1979-2001 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Kauai--Hanalei, 1979-2004 (Box USA23)
    - Kauai--Kaha Lani/Lae Nani, 1979-1989 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Kauai--Poipu, 1978-2001 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Kauai--Princeville, 1987-1999 and undated (Box USA23)
    - Lana'i--General, 1991-2002 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Lana'i--Hotels, 1990-2002 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Lana'i/Molokai, 1975 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Maui--General, 1962-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box USA24)
    - Maui--Activities, 1987-1997 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Maui--Condominuims and hotels, 1993-1997 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Maui--Golf, 1994-1995 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Maui--Hana, 1977-2004 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Maui--Kaanapali, 1974-2002 and undated (Box USA24)
    - Maui--Kapalua, 1989-2001 and undated (Box USA25)
    - Maui--Kihei, 1988-1995 and undated (Box USA25)
    - Maui--Lahaina, 1986-2001 and undated (Box USA25)
    - Maui--Makena, 1988-1997 and undated (Box USA25)
    - Maui--Napili, 1985-1996 (Box USA25)
    - Maui--Wailea, 1984-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA25)
    - Molokai, 1984-2002 and undated (Box USA25)
    - Oahu--General, 1960-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA25)
    - Oahu--General, 1960-2002 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Honolulu, 1994-1997 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Hotels, 1979-2004 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Kahala, 1982-2001 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Ko Olina, 1990-1997 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Makaha, 1980-1982 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Pearl Harbor, 1968 (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Polynesian Cultural Center, 1998-2002 (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels A-Z, 1979-2000 and undated (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Halekulani, 1998-2004 (Box USA26)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Hawaiian Regents, 1983-1993 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Hilton, 1996-2001 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Hyatt, 1980-2001 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Ilikai, 1980-1996 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Prince, 1982-1996 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Royal Hawaiian, 1996-2001 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki Hotels--Sheraton, 1978-2000 (Box USA27)
    - Oahu--Waikiki--Maps, 1981 and undated (Box USA27)
  - Idaho, 190
    - General, 1982-2005 and undated (Box USA27)
    - Sun Valley, 1975-2000 and undated (Box USA27)
  - Illinois, 191
    - General, 1989-2005 and undated (Box USA27)
    - Chicago--General, 1983-2003 and undated (Box USA27)
    - Chicago--Downtown hotels A-L, 1988-2003 and undated (Box USA27)
    - Chicago--Downtown hotels M-Z, 1991-2005 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Chicago--Greater Chicago area, 1987-1994 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Chicago--O'Hare Airport hotels, 1985-1986 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Chicago--Odyssey Cruises, 1993-1996 (Box USA28)
    - Driving trips from Chicago, 1980-1988 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Galena, 1990-2004 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Parks, 2004 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Secretary of State publications, 2000-2001 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Springfield, 1988-2000 (Box USA28)
  - Indiana, 192
    - General, 1959-2000 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Brown County, 1992-1996 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Columbus, 1992-1996 and undated (Box USA28)
    - French Lick Springs, 1967-2002 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Indianapolis, 1996 and undated (Box USA28)
    - Lake/La Porte/Porter counties, 1988-1995 and undated (Box USA29)
  - Iowa, 193
    - General, 1985-2005 and undated (Box USA29)
  - Kansas, 194
    - General, undated (Box USA29)
  - Kentucky, 195
    - General, 1978-2004 and undated (Box USA29)
    - Parks, 1978-1980 (Box USA29)
  - Louisiana, 196
    - General, 1986-2000 and undated (Box USA29)
    - New Orleans--General, 1963-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box USA29)
    - New Orleans--Hotels, 1982-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA29)
  - Maine, 197
    - General, 1977-2005 and undated (Box USA30)
    - Acadia, 1987-1988 (Box USA30)
    - Bar Harbor, 1988-1997 and undated (Box USA30)
  - Maryland, 198
    - General, 1994-2001 (Box USA30)
    - Annapolis, 1987-1996 and undated (Box USA30)
    - Baltimore, 1981-1996 and undated (Box USA30)
    - St. Michael's, 1992-2004 and undated (Box USA30)
  - Massachusetts, 199
    - General, 1986-1999 and undated (Box USA30)
    - Hotels, 1987-2004 and undated (Box USA30)
    - Boston--General, 1990-2000 and undated (Box USA30)
    - Boston--Hotels, 1986-2003 and undated (Box USA31)
    - Canyon Ranch Spa, 1995-2004 (Box USA31)
    - Cape Cod, 1989-1999 and undated (Box USA31)
    - Martha's Vineyard--General, 1968-2002 and undated (Box USA31)
    - Martha's Vineyard--Hotels, 1984-2004 and undated (Box USA31)
    - Martha's Vineyard--Maps, 1995-1997 (Box USA31)
    - Nantucket, 1986-2004 (Box USA31)
  - Michigan, 200
    - General, 1965-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA31)
    - General--Hotels, 1984-2002 and undated (Box USA32)
    - General--Maps, 1973-1997 (Box USA32)
    - Gaylord, 1988-1999 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Harbor Country/Union Pier, 1997-2001 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Henry Ford Museum, 1981-2002 (Box USA32)
    - Holland/Grand Haven, 1991-2001 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Isle Royale, 1981 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Kalamazoo, 1999-2002 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Mackinac Island, 2000-2005 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Parks, 1987-2000 (Box USA32)
    - Saugatuck/Douglas, 2000-2003 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Traverse, 1999-2003 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Upper Peninsula, 2000-2001 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Western Michigan, 2000-2005 (Box USA32)
  - Minnesota, 201
    - General, 1986-2001 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Ely, 1993-1995 and undated (Box USA32)
    - Minneapolis/St. Paul, 1978-2003 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Northeast Minnesota, 1975-1995 (Box USA33)
    - General, 1985-2001 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Hotels, 1975-1990 and undated (Box USA33)
  - Missouri, 202
    - General, 1963-1966 (Box USA33)
    - General--Sightseeing, 1998-2005 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Branson, 1992-2004 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Independence, 2004 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Kansas City, 1983-1991 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Ozarks, 1973-2005 and undated (Box USA33)
    - Pulaski, undated (Box USA33)
    - St. Louis, 1977-2003 and undated (Box USA33)
  - Montana, 203
    - General, 1996-2003 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Big Sky, 1979-1998 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Glacier Park, 1980-1987 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Guest ranches, 1996-2004 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Parks, 1974-1996 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Rail, 1999-2004 (Box USA34)
    - Yellowstone, 1962-1990 and undated (Box USA34)
  - Nebraska, 204
    - General, 1993 and undated (Box USA34)
  - Nevada, 205
    - General, 1969-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA34)
    - Lake Tahoe, 1983-2004 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Las Vegas--General, 1990-2005 and undated (Box USA34)
    - Las Vegas--Hotels, 1990-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA35)
    - Multicultural visitors' guides, 2002-2005 (Box USA35)
    - Nevada Magazine, 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box USA35)
    - Parks, 1980-1994 and undated (Box USA35)
    - Reno, 1982-1997 and undated (Box USA35)
  - New England, 206
    - General, 1987 (Box USA35)
  - New Hampshire, 207
    - General, 1982-2003 and undated (Box USA35)
    - Hotels, 1978-1997 and undated (Box USA35)
    - Maps, 1986-1999 (Box USA35)
    - Official Guidebook, 1999-2002 (Box USA35)
  - New Jersey, 208
    - General, 1987-2002 and undated (Box USA36)
  - New Mexico, 209
    - General, 1971-2003 and undated (Box USA36)
    - General--Attractions, 1994-2001 and undated (Box USA36)
    - General--Hotels, 1991-1995 and undated (Box USA36)
    - General--Maps, 1989 and undated (Box USA36)
    - Albuquerque, 1985-2004 and undated (Box USA36)
    - Parks, 1980-1996 and undated (Box USA36)
    - Santa Fe--General, 1972-2003 and undated (Box USA36)
    - Santa Fe--Hotels, 1981-2003 and undated (Box USA36)
    - Santa Fe--Hotels, 1981-2003 and undated (Box USA37)
    - Santa Fe--Maps, 1993-2004 (Box USA37)
    - Santa Fe--Museum of New Mexico, 1988 and undated (Box USA37)
    - Santa Fe--Opera, 1981-2005 (Box USA37)
    - Taos, 1981-2001 and undated (Box USA37)
  - New York, 210
    - General--Attractions, 1974-2003 and undated (Box USA37)
    - General--Maps, 1960-1978 (Box USA37)
    - Catskills region, 1988-2001 and undated (Box USA37)
    - Cooperstown, 1986-1993 (Box USA37)
    - New York City--General, 1991-2005 and undated (Box USA37)
    - New York City--Attractions, 1960s-2004 and undated (Box USA38)
    - New York City--Hotels A-R, 1984-2005 and undated; 7 folders (Box USA38)
    - New York City--Hotels Ritz-Carlton, 2001-2003 and undated (Box USA39)
    - New York City--Hotels S-Z, 1985-1999 and undated (Box USA39)
    - New York City--Maps, 1960-2001 (Box USA39)
    - New York City--Transportation, 1971-2000 and undated (Box USA39)
    - Resorts--Lake Placid Lodge, 1994 and undated (Box USA39)
    - Resorts--Mirror Lake Inn, 1999-2003 and undated (Box USA39)
    - Resorts--Sagamore (Lake George), 1994-2004 and undated (Box USA39)
    - Resorts--The Point (Saranac), 1996 and undated (Box USA39)
    - Resorts--Villa Roma (Callicoon), 1990-2000 and undated (Box USA39)
  - North Carolina, 211
    - General, 1987-1999 and undated (Box USA39)
    - General--Maps, 1977-1992 (Box USA39)
    - Biltmore Estate, 1976-1991 (Box USA39)
    - Charlotte, 1986-1992 and undated (Box USA40)
    - Great Smoky Mountains, 1977-1994 and undated (Box USA40)
    - Hatteras, 2002 (Box USA40)
    - Outer Banks/Nags Head, 1991-2005; 2 folders (Box USA40)
    - Pinehurst, 1966-2002 and undated (Box USA40)
  - North Dakota, 212
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box USA40)
  - Ohio, 213
    - General, 1960-1992 and undated (Box USA40)
  - Oklahoma, 214
    - General, 1979-1988 and undated (Box USA40)
  - Oregon, 215
    - General, 1980-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA41)
    - Crater Lake, 1950s-1981 (Box USA41)
  - Pennsylvania, 216
    - General, 1975-1996 and undated (Box USA41)
    - Nemacolin Woodlands, 1999-2004 and undated (Box USA41)
    - Philadelphia, 1966-1996 and undated (Box USA41)
    - Poconos, 1982-2005 and undated (Box USA41)
  - Rhode Island, 217
    - General, 1958-1996 and undated (Box USA41)
    - Newport, 1978-2004 and undated (Box USA41)
  - South Carolina, 218
    - General, 1982-2005 and undated (Box USA41)
    - General--Maps, 1992-1994 (Box USA42)
    - Charleston--General, 1975-2002 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Charleston--Attractions, 1989-2003 (Box USA42)
    - Charleston--Hotels, 1987-2001 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Charleston--Seabrook Island, 1992-1998 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Hilton Head--General, 1984-2003 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Hilton Head--Hotels, 1971-2003 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Hilton Head--Sea Pines, 1985-1992 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Kiawah Island, 1994-2004 and undated (Box USA42)
    - Litchfield, 1986-2002 (Box USA42)
    - Myrtle Beach--General, 1991-2003 and undated (Box USA43)
    - Myrtle Beach--Golf, 1996-2004 (Box USA43)
    - Myrtle Beach--Sands resort, 2002-2004 and undated (Box USA43)
    - Myrtle Beach--Vacation guides, 2001 (Box USA43)
  - South Dakota, 219
    - General, 1973-2000 and undated (Box USA43)
    - Maps, 1982-1998 and undated (Box USA43)
    - Parks, 1938-1992 and undated (Box USA43)
  - Tennessee, 220
    - General, 1987-2002 and undated (Box USA43)
    - Blackberry Farm, 1993-2004 and undated (Box USA43)
    - Blackberry Farm, 1993-2004 and undated (Box USA44)
    - Gatlinburg/Memphis/Smokies, 1976-2002 and undated (Box USA44)
    - Nashville, 1979-2004 and undated (Box USA44)
  - Texas, 221
    - General--Attractions, 1972-2005 and undated (Box USA44)
    - General--Hotels, 1982-2005 and undated (Box USA44)
    - General--Tour guides, 1987-2005 (Box USA44)
    - Austin--General, 1992-2003 (Box USA44)
    - Austin--Hotels, 1978-2002 and undated (Box USA44)
    - Austin--Lake Austin, 2002-2004 and undated (Box USA44)
    - Corpus Christi, 1960s-1987 and undated (Box USA44)
    - Dallas--General, 1975-1996 and undated (Box USA44)
    - Dallas--Hotels, 1981-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA45)
    - Fort Worth, 1988 and undated (Box USA45)
    - Galveston, 1976-1995 and undated (Box USA45)
    - Houston, 1976-1999 and undated (Box USA45)
    - Padre Island/Brownsville, 1977-2000 and undated (Box USA45)
    - Parks (Big Bend), 1991-1994 (Box USA45)
    - San Antonio--General, 1981-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA45)
    - San Antonio--Hotels, 1993-2000 and undated (Box USA45)
  - Utah, 222
    - General, 1998-2002 and undated (Box USA46)
    - Green Valley Spa (St. George), undated (Box USA46)
    - Park City--General, 2004-2005 and undated (Box USA46)
    - Park City--Resorts, 1991-2005 and undated (Box USA46)
    - Parks, 1971-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA46)
    - Resorts/Hotels, 1977-2002 and undated (Box USA46)
    - Salt Lake/Salt Lake City, 1996-2002 and undated (Box USA46)
  - Vermont, 223
    - General, 1976-2003 and undated (Box USA46)
    - General, 1976-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA47)
    - General--Hotels, 1991-2005 and undated (Box USA47)
    - Equinox, 1999-2003 and undated (Box USA47)
    - Smuggler's Notch, 1990-2004 (Box USA47)
    - Stowe, 1971-2002 and undated (Box USA47)
    - Sugarbush, 1972-1993 and undated (Box USA47)
    - Woodstock, 1980-2003 and undated (Box USA47)
  - Virginia, 224
    - General, 1964-1995 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA48)
    - General--Attractions, 1986-2003 and undated (Box USA48)
    - General--Hotels, 1980-2004 and undated (Box USA48)
    - Charlottesville, 1987-2005 and undated (Box USA48)
    - Homestead/Hot Springs, 1987-2005 and undated (Box USA48)
    - Norfolk, 1982-1994 and undated (Box USA48)
    - Shenandoah, 1994 and undated (Box USA48)
    - Virginia Beach, 1980-2003 and undated (Box USA48)
    - Williamsburg--Attractions, 1975-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA48)
    - Williamsburg--Hotels, 1974-2003 and undated (Box USA48)
  - Washington, 225
    - General, 1982-1998 and undated (Box USA49)
    - General--Hotels, 1982-2001 and undated (Box USA49)
    - General--Parks, 1972-1994 (Box USA49)
    - Rosario, 1986-1994 and undated (Box USA49)
    - Seattle, 1982-2004 and undated (Box USA49)
  - West Virginia, 226
    - General, 1976 and undated (Box USA49)
    - Greenbrier, 1974-2006 and undated (Box USA49)
  - Wisconsin, 227